A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Office of the Vice President, Office Files of Francis X. Sutton FA568
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program Files, 1952-1985, bulk 1967-1985; 1967-1985; II
  - Development Planning and Management -- Employment Study -- Memoranda, Reports, Meeting Materials Re: Employment in Developing Countries and FF Aid (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Development Planning and Management -- Employment Study -- Memoranda, Reports, Meeting Materials Re: Employment in Developing Countries and FF Aid (2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Development Planning and Management -- Employment Study -- Report, "Employment in Developing Countries" by Edgar O. Edwards, 1973 August (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Development Planning and Management -- Employment Study -- Reports, Articles, 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Education -- Bellagio Education Meeting (9/16-18/75) -- Papers (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Education -- Bellagio Education Meeting (9/16-18/75) -- Papers, Memoranda, Agendas (folder 2 of 2), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Education -- Bellagio Plus (Oct, 1975) -- Notes, Meeting Materials, 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Education -- Education and Development Third Meeting -- Working Paper, 1976 June 27-29 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Education -- General -- Memoranda, Notes, Background Re: Bellagio Meetings, Budgets, etc. (1 of 2), 1969-1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Education -- General -- Memoranda, Notes, Background Re: Bellagio Meetings, Budgets, etc. (2 of 2), 1969-1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Education -- Guidelines and Understanding Re: Educational Development -- Memoranda, Notes, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Education -- Information Paper for the Trustee Committee on Education and Public Policy, "The Arts Program", 1980 March (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Education -- International Division Support for Third World Scholars Evaluation -- Memoranda, Notes, 1977 November 30-1978 March 30 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Center for Applied Linguistics -- Memoranda, 1971-1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Language Development Study Group Papers (1 of 3), 1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Language Development Study Group Papers (2 of 3), 1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Language Development Study Group Papers (3 of 3), 1967 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes Re: Language Meetings and Foundation Language Activities, 1967-1972 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Report on Language Deliberations Re: Overseas Activities in Language Fields (1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Report on Language Deliberations Re: Overseas Activities in Language Fields (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Report, "Ford Foundation Foreign or Second Language Activities in the Unites States and Overseas, 1951-1966" by Melvin J. Fox, 1967 May-June (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Report, "A Gloss on Fox: Some Implications of the Fox Report for Foundation Activities in the Language Field and Proposals for Follow-Up", 1968 January 8 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Report, "Language and Development: A Retrospective Survey of Ford Foundation Language Projects, 1952-1974" by Melvin J. Fox (separated), 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Retrospective Language Survey -- Background Documents Packet incl. Memoranda, Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Retrospective Language Survey -- Memoranda, Reports Re: Survey Progress Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Education -- Language Study -- Retrospective Language Survey -- Proposal/Report Re: Kenya Language Project by Roderick J. Hemphill, 1973 October 16 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Education -- Report for the Special Program in Education Division, "A Review of the Special Program of Capital Grants to Universities and Colleges" by Reuben Frodin, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Education -- Report for the Education and Research Division, "Dimensions of Recent Growth in Private Universities and Colleges" by Reuben Frodin, 1968 September (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Education -- Report, "Report of the Task Force on National Manpower Targets for Advanced Research on Foreign Areas" by the National Council on Foreign Language and International Studies, 1981 November (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Education -- University of London Seminar -- The Commonwealth as an Education Network -- Correspondence, Discussion Papers, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Education -- Ward, F. Champion Materials -- Education Conference Information, Memoranda, Background (1 of 3), 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Education -- Ward, F. Champion Materials -- Education Conference Information, Memoranda, Background (2 of 3), 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Education -- Ward, F. Champion Materials -- Education Conference Information, Memoranda, Background (3 of 3), 1976-1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Education -- Ward, F. Champion Materials -- "An Exile's Report", 1976 February 23 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Education and Culture -- Memoranda, Notes, Budget Proposals Re: Creation of Combined Program, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Canadian and European Grant Lists, 1968-1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Common Problems -- Memoranda, 1967-1972 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- East European Program -- Memoranda, Meeting Information, Notes, Grant Projections, etc. (1 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- East European Program -- Memoranda, Meeting Information, Notes, Grant Projections, etc. (2 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- East European Program -- Memoranda, Meeting Information, Notes, Grant Projections, etc. (3 of 3), 1968-1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Eastern Europe and Soviet Union -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes Re: Trips, Grants, Programs incl. IREX (1 of 3), 1967-1980 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Eastern Europe and Soviet Union -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes Re: Trips, Grants, Programs incl. IREX (2 of 3), 1967-1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Eastern Europe and Soviet Union -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes Re: Trips, Grants, Programs incl. IREX (3 of 3), 1967-1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Foundation Programs in Europe Conference (Feb 1971) -- Agenda, Memoranda, Papers, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- General -- Discussion Papers, Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Grant and Trip Reports, Program Planning, Meetings, etc. (1 of 4), 1967-1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- General -- Discussion Papers, Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Grant and Trip Reports, Program Planning, Meetings, etc. (2 of 4), 1971 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- General -- Discussion Papers, Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Grant and Trip Reports, Program Planning, Meetings, etc. (3 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- General -- Discussion Papers, Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Grant and Trip Reports, Program Planning, Meetings, etc. (4 of 4), 1975-1981 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- International Meetings -- Discussion Papers, Memoranda, 1967-1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Italy -- Memoranda, Notes Re: Student Unrest, Foundations, etc., 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Paris Office -- Memoranda Re: Office Opening, Information Paper, 1967-1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Program Reviews -- Memoranda, Discussion Notes, Budget Paper, etc., 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Report, "Planning for the Foundation's Activities in Europe", 1967 December (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Southern Europe -- Itineraries for Visit, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Europe and International Affairs (EIA) -- Spain -- Trip Report, 1968 October 23-November 19 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Ford Foundation -- Annual Report, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Grantmaking -- Grants to Terminating Ford Foundation Employees -- Memoranda, Reports, Grant Requests, 1973-1981 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Grantmaking -- International Training and Research and International Affairs Unpaid Grants through 1966 -- List, 1966-1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Grantmaking -- Issues -- Relationship Between Ford Foundation Activities and United States Government Programs -- Memoranda, Reports, 1969 March (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Grantmaking -- Issues -- Policy Changes Re: Individual Awards, Foundation Grants to Government Officials and Private Foundations -- Memoranda, Reports, 1969 April-November (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Grantmaking -- Issues -- Legal Status of International Organization Grantees -- Memoranda, Notes, 1969 July-August (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Grantmaking -- Issues -- Possible Controversial Grants -- Memoranda, 1969 September (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Grantmaking -- Issues -- Lists of Foreign and Domestic Grantees/Funding Qualifications Checklist, circa 1969 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Grantmaking -- Management and Trends -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes (1 of 3), 1970-1981 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Grantmaking -- Management and Trends -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes (2 of 3), 1970-1981 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Grantmaking -- Management and Trends -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes (3 of 3), 1970-1981 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Grantmaking -- Survey of Noteworthy Grants, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda Re: Distasteful Regimes, Athens Press Conference Background, Relationship with CIA, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda, Reports, Background Re: Latin America and the Philippines, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda Re: International Committee Meeting, IREX Correspondence, Budget Proposals, 1975 January-March (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda Re: Intellectual Communications, Conversations, Human Rights Draft Report, Notes, 1975 August-October (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda Re: Meetings, Board Paper, Background Papers, 1975 November (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda Re: Proposed Meeting, Information Paper, Notes, Background Material, 1975 December (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda Re: Survey Magazine, Committee Meetings, Meeting Minutes; Correspondence, etc., 1976 January-May (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda Re: Survey Magazine, Argentina; Grant Actions, 1976 June (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda, Minutes, Grant Actions Re: Committee on Human Rights and Social Process, 1976 August-September (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda Re: South Africa, Discussion Papers, Grant Actions, Committee Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1976 October-December (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda Re: Committee Meetings and Foundation Work, Notes, Reports, Correspondence Re: International Seminar, 1977 January-July (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Human Rights -- Correspondence, Notes, Reports, Grant Actions, 1977 August-December (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda, Information Paper, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Human Rights -- Memoranda Re: Trustees Committee, Information Paper, Grant Actions, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Human Rights -- Miscellaneous Handwritten Notes, 1973-1979 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - International Committee of the Board of Trustees -- "Foundation Programs in Europe" Conference (2/24-25/1971) -- Papers Re: Foundation Work in Europe (1 of 4) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - International Committee of the Board of Trustees -- "Foundation Programs in Europe" Conference (2/24-25/1971) -- Papers Re: Education and Research in Europe (2 of 4), 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - International Committee of the Board of Trustees -- "Foundation Programs in Europe" Conference (2/24-25/1971) -- Papers Re: Humanities and the Arts (3 of 4), 1970 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - International Committee of the Board of Trustees -- "Foundation Programs in Europe" Conference (2/24-25/1971) -- Papers Re: Population Grants, AP/LAC/MEA Interest in Europe, Conference Summary (4 of 4) (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - International Division -- Division Reserve -- Memoranda, Grant Lists (1 of 2), 1979 May-1980 June (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - International Division -- Division Reserve -- Memoranda, Proposals, Grant Information (2 of 2), 1980 September-1981 September (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - International Division -- "Fairwell to International Division" Party -- Memoranda, Invitation List, 1981 August-October (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - International Division -- Foundation for International Technical Cooperation (FITC-ISTC) -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Proposal, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - International Division -- General Reserve, ID Reserve, ID Program Budget Summaries, ID Program Management Costs, 1967-1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - International Division -- General Reserve -- Memoranda Re: Grant Recommendations and Budgeting (1 of 2), 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - International Division -- General Reserve -- Memoranda Re: Grant Recommendations and Budgeting (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - International Division -- Memoranda Re: Grant Distribution, Program Management Consultants, Foreign Currencies, Office of the Vice President Reports, 1967-1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - International Division -- Memoranda Re: Immigration and Nationality Act, Legal Basis of FF International Work, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - International Division -- Memoranda, Reports Re: Nelson-Zeidenstein Paper on Division Organization (incl. Nelson-Zeidenstein Paper), 1970 January-June (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - International Division -- Memoranda Re: New Program Categories/Division Organization, 1970 June-August (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - International Division -- Memoranda Re: Training Associates Program and Overseas Personnel, 1970 June-November (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - International Division -- Memoranda Re: Foundation Audit Program, 1971 May-June (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - International Division -- Memoranda Re: Research Support Procedures, 1971 March-September (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - International Division -- Memoranda Re: Production of Grant Reports, Procedures, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - International Division -- Office of the Vice President -- Program Reviews -- Background Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - International Division -- Reorganization -- Memoranda, Discussion Papers, Background (1 of 4), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - International Division -- Reorganization -- Memoranda, Discussion Papers, Background (2 of 4), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - International Division -- Reorganization -- Memoranda, Discussion Papers, Background (3 of 4), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - International Division -- Reorganization -- Memoranda, Discussion Papers, Background (4 of 4), 1981 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - International Division -- Resource Bases -- Reports; Memoranda Re: Grantmaking, Budgets; Proposals (1 of 4), 1967 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - International Division -- Resource Bases -- Reports; Memoranda Re: Grantmaking, Budgets; Proposals (2 of 4), 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - International Division -- Resource Bases -- Reports; Memoranda Re: Grantmaking, Budgets; Proposals (3 of 4), 1967 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - International Division -- Resource Bases -- Reports; Memoranda Re: Grantmaking, Budgets; Proposals (4 of 4), 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - International Division -- Resource Bases (Regional and Non-Regional) -- Office of the Vice President -- Memoranda, Notes, Budget Projections, Reports (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - International Division -- Resource Bases (Regional and Non-Regional) -- Office of the Vice President -- Memoranda, Notes, Budget Projections, Reports (2 of 2), 1968-1972 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - International Division -- Resource Bases -- Universities as Resource Bases -- Memoranda, Draft Paper, 1968-1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - International Division -- Universities --Transitional Program -- Memoranda, Site Visits, Reports, Grant Recommendations (1 of 3), 1970-1974 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - International Division -- Universities --Transitional Program -- Memoranda, Site Visits, Reports, Grant Recommendations (2 of 3), 1970-1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - International Division -- Universities --Transitional Program -- Memoranda, Site Visits, Reports, Grant Recommendations (3 of 3), 1970-1974 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - International Division -- Ward, F. Champion Materials -- Reminiscences of International Work, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Coordinating Committee 1975 Annual Report, 1976 June (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Manpower Planning -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes, Proposals, etc. (1 of 3), 1970-1973 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Manpower Planning -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes, Proposals, etc. (2 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Manpower Planning -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes, Proposals, etc. (3 of 3), 1975-1979 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Report, "Survey of Foundation and Government Grants for Women's Rights and Opportunities, 1971-1975", 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Report, "Feminism in 1975: The Non-Establishment, the Establishment, and the Future" by Maren Lockwood Carden, 1976 March (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Report, "The International Division's Women's Program - Interim Report" by Elinor G. Barber, 1977 March (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Report, "Review of Grant-Making for Women's Issues in the 1970's: Past Patterns and Future Priorities" by Rosabeth Moss Kanter, et al., 1977 April 30 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Report, "Ford Foundation Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs", 1978 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Report, "Report on Affirmative Action", 1979 March (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Report, "Ford Foundation Programs for Women: Plans and Budgets for Fiscal Years 1980 and 1981", 1980 March (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Sub-Committee on Women and Minorities -- Memoranda Re: Appointments, Meetings, 1975 September-December (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Women's Meeting -- Memoranda, Papers Re: Program Estimates, etc. (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Women's Meeting -- Memoranda, Papers Re: Program Estimates, etc. (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - International Division -- Women's Programs -- Women's Program Group -- Memoranda, 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - International Economic Order -- International Policy Research Institute -- Memoranda, Notes, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - International Economic Order -- Memoranda, Reports, Meeting Notes, Grant Lists, 1972-1980 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - International Economic Order -- Report, "The Foundation's Program Concerned with the World Economy", 1980 June (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - International Economic Order Review -- Memoranda, Notes, 1967-1973 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - International Studies -- American and European Studies -- Memoranda, Notes, 1967-1975 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - International Studies -- Conference Re: International Studies in Europe (Oct 1974) -- Background Papers (folder 1 of 3) (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - International Studies -- Conference Re: International Studies in Europe (Oct 1974) -- Background Papers (2 of 3), 1974 October (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - International Studies -- Conference Re: International Studies in Europe (Oct 1974) -- Background Papers (3 of 3), 1974 October (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - International Studies -- Conference Re: International Studies in Europe (5/26-27/1975) -- Memoranda, Notes, Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - International Studies -- Foreign Area Training Fellows -- Research Topics, 1967 February-April (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - International Studies -- Grant List (ITR Approvals of Selected Universities), 1969 January 22 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - International Studies -- Grant List and Summary -- Appropriation Control (FY 1981) (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - International Studies -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes Re: Social Science Research Council, American Universities, Foundation Objectives, Language Studies, 1967-1980 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - International Studies -- Report for International Division Conference (3/21-24/1979), "International Studies in Other Countries" by Felice Gaer, 1979 March (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - International Studies -- Robert McCaughey Book Re: Ford Foundation, International Studies, the University and American Learning -- Memoranda, Chapter Outlines, Data (1 of 4), 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - International Studies -- Robert McCaughey Book Re: Ford Foundation, International Studies, the University and American Learning -- Correspondence, Report, Draft Chapters (2 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - International Studies -- Robert McCaughey Book Re: Ford Foundation, International Studies, the University and American Learning -- Correspondence, Draft Chapter, Data (3 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - International Studies -- Robert McCaughey Book Re: Ford Foundation, International Studies, the University and American Learning -- Draft Chapter, Comments (4 of 4), 1982 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - International Studies Review -- Consultants -- Correspondence Re: Appointments, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - International Studies Review -- Federal Funding -- Correspondence, Memoranda Re: ACLS/SSRC, 1969-1973 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - International Studies Review -- Foreign Area Fellowship Program (FAFP), Social Science Research Council (SSRC), and International Research and Exchanges (IREX) -- Memoranda, Reports, 1967-1975 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - International Studies Review -- IREX Conference (5/10-13/1979) -- Schedule, Papers (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - International Studies Review -- International Training and Research -- Swayzee Report, Memoranda, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - International Studies Review -- Libraries -- Memoranda, 1967-1973 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - International Studies Review -- Memoranda, Reports Re: Foundation Support, Survey Trips, Review Meetings, Consultant Work (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - International Studies Review -- Memoranda, Reports Re: Foundation Support, Survey Trips, Review Meetings, Consultant Work (2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - International Studies Review -- National Defense Education Act (NDEA) -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Report Re: Impact of Federal Budget Cuts, 1971-1976 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) -- Caribbean Program Review -- Reports, Memoranda, Meeting Minutes, Background (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) -- Caribbean Program Review -- Reports, Memoranda, Meeting Minutes, Background (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) -- Reorganization -- Memoranda, Discussion Papers (1 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 34, Folder 2)